motionglobal.com 2006-08-19

# Motion Global

                               **MOTION GLOBAL Privacy Policy effective MARCH 1, 2005.**

MOTION GLOBAL is committed to respecting your privacy. We've structured our Web site so that, in general, you can visit MOTION GLOBAL on the Web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. Once you choose to provide us personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified), you can be assured that it will only be used to support your customer relationship with MOTION GLOBAL.

This statement regarding the privacy of the personally identifiable information you provide online covers four main areas: Awareness, Choice, Accuracy & Access and Security. 

**Awareness**

MOTION GLOBAL provides this Online Privacy Statement to make you aware of our privacy policy and practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and from the bottom of every page on our Web site. 

**What we collect**

We do not collect your E-mail address unless you contact us by E-mail or volunteer your E-mail address and other personal information. 

We do collect "cookies" to store your preferences and record session information.

On MOTION GLOBAL Web site, you can order products or services, make requests and register to receive materials. 

In order to tailor our subsequent communications to you and continuously improve our products and services, we may also ask you to voluntarily provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experience with our products and contact preferences. 

**How we use it**

MOTION GLOBAL uses your information to better understand your needs and provide you with better service. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction, to communicate back to you, to update you on services and benefits, and to personalize our Web sites for you. Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and are not retained for other purposes 

From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research or to provide you with marketing information we think would be of particular interest. At a minimum, we will always give you the opportunity to opt out of receiving such direct marketing or market research contact. We will also follow local requirements, such as allowing you to opt in before receiving unsolicited contact, where applicable. Data collected online may also be combined with information you provide when you enroll with MOTION GLOBAL.

**Whom we share it with**

MOTION GLOBAL will not sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information to others unless we have your permission or are required by law. We will only share the personal data you provide online with other MOTION GLOBAL entities and/or business partners who are acting on our behalf for the uses described above. Such MOTION GLOBAL entities and/or business partners, including those in AUSTRALIA & HONG KONG and/or any other countries, are governed by our privacy policies with respect to the use of this data and are bound by the appropriate confidentiality agreements.

**Choice**

MOTION GLOBAL will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without first letting you know and offering you a choice. As previously stated, we will also provide you the opportunity to let us know if you do not wish to receive unsolicited direct marketing materials from us and we will do everything we can to honor such requests. 

Your permission is always secured first, should we ever share your information with third parties that are not acting on our behalf and governed by our privacy policy.

**Accuracy & Access**

MOTION GLOBAL strives to keep your personally identifiable information accurate and secure. We do not provide access to your information online. In order to update or correct your information with MOTION GLOBAL it will be necessary for you to contact MOTION GLOBAL directly through the methods listed below. To protect your privacy and security, upon contacting us we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access or enabling you to make corrections.

At present, MOTION GLOBAL does not offer links to third-party Web sites.

**Security**

MOTION GLOBAL is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We use the latest in encryption technology when collecting or transferring sensitive data, such as credit card information.

**International Use**

Information that is submitted to MOTION GLOBAL's Web Site will be collected, processed, stored, disclosed, and disposed of in accordance with applicable Australian law. In addition, such information may be stored on servers located outside your resident jurisdiction. By providing us with your information, you acknowledge that you have read this Policy, understand it, agree to its terms and consent to the transfer of such information outside your resident jurisdiction. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use the MOTION GLOBAL Web Site.

**Future Developments**

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.
